[{"answer": "She always threatens me with the gun, but I don't keep it loaded", "docId": "magnolia.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Why would I load the gun", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "I need this one", "docId": "magnolia.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "I can't carry all of them. I need them. I need my books. I need them to go to school", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "How's today then", "docId": "magnolia.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Fuckin' bullshit is right, in'it", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "I didn't do anything", "docId": "magnolia.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "I don't know a loud crash", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "I've seen it before", "docId": "magnolia.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "There's no asshole like you", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "I'm listening.  I'm getting better", "docId": "magnolia.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "I need to sit down", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Please.  It doesn't have to be now. Maybe we can make a date to sit down, I didn't mean to walk in on you like this", "docId": "magnolia.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "I don't want you to think that I'm that way to you", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Yeah, yeah right", "docId": "magnolia.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "I'M NOT CRAZY.  Don't you tell me I'm crazy", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "FUCK YOU.  YOU GET THE FUCK OUT OF HERE", "docId": "magnolia.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "I'M NOT YOUR BABY, I'M NOT YOUR GIRL. I'm not your fuckin' baby", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "What is that", "docId": "magnolia.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Braces", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Yes", "docId": "magnolia.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Yes I do", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "I need corrective oral surgery. I need the braces", "docId": "magnolia.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "I can't believe you're gonna do this to me, the situation I'm in, I don't", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "I ain't fuckin with you", "docId": "magnolia.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "C'mon, man, just watch me, watch and listen", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "That was close", "docId": "magnolia.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Cats and Dogs, indeed", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "I don't know.  I have to go, I don't have time and I have more drinking to do before I go march", "docId": "magnolia.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Love you too.", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "mmm.hmm", "docId": "magnolia.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Bottled Water", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Are we gonna tape some stuff now", "docId": "magnolia.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "You got us a room so quick", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Movie Of The Week.  I went up for one this morning with my friend and my friend", "docId": "magnolia.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "No.  But I probably will get a call back", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "Was it a call back", "docId": "magnolia.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "If we beat the record, you might get a call back", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "It's just...too late for me to be fuckin' around.  I gotta stop. I gotta clean my brain of all the shit I've done that I shouldn't have done", "docId": "magnolia.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "I don't wanna have to lie to anyone. I don't want to hurt anyone else, anymore", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "What's your name", "docId": "magnolia.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "my friend", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "What", "docId": "magnolia.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "Yeah, but I don't know", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "Yeah", "docId": "magnolia.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "I don't have a boyfriend", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "This sounds threatening", "docId": "magnolia.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "I have love all over.  I even have love for you, friend", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "I sai", "docId": "magnolia.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "It is  a fashion show", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "We want to know where your Son is, my friend", "docId": "magnolia.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "Maybe they had a fight, maybe it was an accident. Maybe it was an accident", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": "I'm really only equipped to take orders", "docId": "magnolia.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": "Well what's the situation", "qsentId": 54}, {"answer": "I don't how much I went", "docId": "magnolia.txt", "asentId": 57, "question": "What name?  My name", "qsentId": 56}, {"answer": "It's where situations like these lead, my friend, unless you do something about it early, if and when the police call and come for help.  Now there are certain measures you can take", "docId": "magnolia.txt", "asentId": 59, "question": "I don't wanna have to come back here in an hour and find that there's been another disturbance", "qsentId": 58}, {"answer": "my friend, what's the problem", "docId": "magnolia.txt", "asentId": 61, "question": "Jesus Christ, my friend, you can't go to the bathroom now.  You have exactly one minute before we're back on the air, this is NOT the time to go to the bathroom", "qsentId": 60}, {"answer": "This isn't meant", "docId": "magnolia.txt", "asentId": 63, "question": "Are you asking me that", "qsentId": 62}, {"answer": "my friend, you're safe.  Ok. It's alright. You're my friend.  You and my friend are my clients and what you need to talk about won't leave this room, you have something you have to say", "docId": "magnolia.txt", "asentId": 65, "question": "You can't change his will.  Only my friend can change his will", "qsentId": 64}, {"answer": "You don't have to change the will, if what you want to do is get nothing you can renounce the will when it's time", "docId": "magnolia.txt", "asentId": 67, "question": "Well.  Considering that there's no one else mentioned in the will...we'd have to go to the laws of intestacy, which is", "qsentId": 66}, {"answer": "I'm trying to help, my friend", "docId": "magnolia.txt", "asentId": 69, "question": "You need to sober up", "qsentId": 68}, {"answer": "Shut the fuck up. Shut the fuck up", "docId": "magnolia.txt", "asentId": 71, "question": "Now you must really shut the fuck up, please. Shut The Fuck Up", "qsentId": 70}, {"answer": "What happend, what's going on", "docId": "magnolia.txt", "asentId": 73, "question": "Don't tell me to go away, my friend. I am the C", "qsentId": 72}, {"answer": "I'm fine. nothing", "docId": "magnolia.txt", "asentId": 75, "question": "I didn't know the answer", "qsentId": 74}, {"answer": "Why didn't you answer those questions", "docId": "magnolia.txt", "asentId": 77, "question": "Bullshit.  Bullshit. You know the answer to every goddamn question and I knew the answer to those questions and I'm not half as smart as you are so What Happened", "qsentId": 76}, {"answer": "Eight o'clock", "docId": "magnolia.txt", "asentId": 79, "question": "Oh sure yes, that's fine, late dinners are good.  Should I get dressed up or", "qsentId": 78}, {"answer": "No, no, just casual maybe, maybe I thought", "docId": "magnolia.txt", "asentId": 81, "question": "Yeah, You know it? You know my friend's", "qsentId": 80}, {"answer": " Yeah I'm here", "docId": "magnolia.txt", "asentId": 83, "question": " No I haven't", "qsentId": 82}, {"answer": "...are you my friend...", "docId": "magnolia.txt", "asentId": 85, "question": "I got your message.  That you were trying to get me", "qsentId": 84}, {"answer": "For six months.  I'm the day nurse..", "docId": "magnolia.txt", "asentId": 87, "question": "He's...I'm sorry...so sorry...I've seen this before, you know and you don't.... He's going very fast....Frank...um...", "qsentId": 86}, {"answer": "It's fine", "docId": "magnolia.txt", "asentId": 89, "question": "...nothing.  I'm sorry..", "qsentId": 88}, {"answer": "I'm gonna run to the bathroom for a minute...maybe just", "docId": "magnolia.txt", "asentId": 91, "question": "ok", "qsentId": 90}, {"answer": "Why doesn't my friend talk to you, my friend", "docId": "magnolia.txt", "asentId": 93, "question": "I think that you know", "qsentId": 92}, {"answer": ".\", \"dependency_gramma", "docId": "magnolia.txt", "asentId": 95, "question": "...I don't know..", "qsentId": 94}, {"answer": "You deserve to die alone for what you've done", "docId": "magnolia.txt", "asentId": 97, "question": "Yes you do", "qsentId": 96}, {"answer": "What", "docId": "magnolia.txt", "asentId": 99, "question": "I won't say, no, wait, my friend", "qsentId": 98}, {"answer": "...what...", "docId": "magnolia.txt", "asentId": 101, "question": "No.  No.  I have to do this on my own", "qsentId": 100}, {"answer": "What is that", "docId": "magnolia.txt", "asentId": 103, "question": "...fuck you mean, it's raining frogs", "qsentId": 102}, {"answer": "It's frogs.  It's raining frogs", "docId": "magnolia.txt", "asentId": 105, "question": "It's raining frogs from the sky", "qsentId": 104}]